Brother, how are you?
Thank you!
What happened to this building?
The building just 'hooked up' just like that because of the enemies; my father's people.
The building just what?
It 'hooked up' since 2008 after I roofed it.
Immediately you started that building, everything, including your business, just collapsed.
Yes.
Because we should ask God before making an attempt or step forward to do something.
Money should not be the one to control our spiritual life; we should allow the Giver of money to control us.
Sometimes you want to go to the village and do something,
instead of you to stay still, prepare your life and be strong in the Lord.
Suddenly, one collapses there.
So, there is need to ask God in every step that we are taking.
What about this court case?
It has gone.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Go and call your wife because I am seeing a baby boy.
She is not here!
Dont worry!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
People of God, Emmanuel!
I thank God for being here today,
and I thank Prophet T.B. Joshua, the man of God, the prophet of our time.
Without the prophecy of the man of God, I don't know where I would have been.
A nation without a prophet is finished!
A country without a prophet is finished!
It happened like this:
My name is Mr Michael Ugwu and the woman beside me is my lovely wife,
Mrs Favour Ugwu, and my son Peter Ugwu.
On the 27th of April 2014, I was sitting in the church and the Man of God was prophesying.
Luckily for me, he came across me and asked me, "What about that house? What happened?"
I told him that I went into that project, I got connected.
Then, temptations were all around me and many problems.
He also asked me about the court case, it's all about my land.
I was living outside Nigeria before.
This land - the people who sold it to me wanted to take it back from me again.
After that, it was like he wanted to leave me then he asked, "Where is your wife?"
I told him that my wife was not there.
I didn't know that as I was here, my wife was in the house watching Emmanuel TV!
That is the only TV station we watch in our house.
The Man of God said to me, "I am seeing a baby boy".
I never told the man of God my problem, that we were barren.
We were barren for six years.
I met my wife in 2011; since we met as husband and wife, there has been no child.
We faced the problem of barrenness for six years.
Luckily for me, on that fateful day, my problem came to an end.
The Man of God said, "I am seeing a baby boy."
I held onto that word in faith and I believed that that day my problem was over.
Could you imagine...
When I got back to my house, I prayed with my wife with the Morning Water.
I met with my wife and suddenly my wife became pregnant.
I couldn't believe it.
I was like, "It's not me". My wife said, "I am pregnant".
I said, "No, you are not pregnant".
Since then, everything has just been (well).
After nine months, my wife delivered our baby peacefully.
She was having multiple fibroids, and the doctor said he would operate her.
My wife said no; rather, she believed in the Morning Water from The SCOAN.
My wife anointed herself with the Morning Water.
To my surprise, she delivered this bouncing baby boy.
This is the baby boy the man of God talked about when he said, "I'm seeing a baby boy".
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Testimony Time
Since then, my life has changed.
Since we had our baby boy, a lot of blessings and doors have opened in my business.
In the last three weeks, I bought this car.
I bought this car for them to use, showing appreciation for what God is doing in my family and my life.
Since then, a lot of doors have opened - contacts.
I don't know what to say!
Testimony Time
Amen. Indeed, a million thanks are not enough!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Testimony Time
In that word of prophecy, the man of God first of all mentioned the issue of a building.
Can you explain to us - after the prophecy, what has happened concerning that building?
After receiving the prophecy about my buildings - there were two buildings.
I had not even roofed the buildings because money to pay for roofers was a problem.
I had a lot of jobs to do for that project but I could not get them finished.
After the prophecy, how it happened I don't know, I was able to finish everything.
I did not come with the picture because I did not know that I would be here today to give this testimony.
So you mean that the building that the man of God prophesied about
that everything had stopped, you have now completed it and it is finished.
It is finished, everything is finished!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
Testimony Time
Sir, when you saw your wife deliver this baby boy,
were you not surprised considering that Prophet T.B. Joshua gave you this prophecy
when your wife was not pregnant and told you the exact gender of the child in her womb that was going to come.
Were you not shocked when your wife delivered and you saw that it was a baby boy?
That is why we are here because I am surprised.
Even though the Man of God did not know my problem,
he prophesied to me, "I am seeing a baby boy".
After that prophecy, I was surprised when my wife delivered
this beautiful baby boy, by my side here.
I am surprised. I thank God!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
That is the power of the prophetic word. We can all be a witness to this
that it can only be by the hand of God that can reveal something of this nature.
The sex of a child that had not at that time even entered the womb of our brother's wife,
the Man of God prophesied and it came to pass, and we give all the glory to our Lord Jesus Christ.
At this point, we want to hear a word from your wife as well.
People of God, Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mrs Favour Ugwu.
I want to thank God for the prophecy.
That day, I was at home. When he asked, "Where is your wife?",
I was in the parlour watching him.
He asked, "Where is your wife?" He said, "My wife is at home".
He then said, "I see a baby boy coming".
I jumped up and started shouting.
Immediately, I dressed up and started coming here.
When I reached here, he prayed for us; that was in 2014.
We continued praying and at the end of the year 2015, I conceived.
During the pregnancy, I did not bother to go to the hospital for tests or scans.
I didn't bother to go because I was sure that what the Man of God said was true.
At the eighth month, I went for a scan. By then, I had finished buying everything.
People were asking me why I was buying only male things and not female's.
I told them that I was sure of what I was buying because God had already said it.
Even the doctor questioned why I did not want to go for the scan, saying that I was stingy.
I said I was not stingy but the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua had already said it.
He told my husband, "This is a baby boy coming".
Before then, I was praying for a baby girl.
But immediately he said it, I removed my mind from it.
I was buying clothes for a male child.
That day, the doctor asked me to go for a scan but I said that I didn't want to.
At the eighth month, I went for a scan so that I would have a copy of it.
Before then, the doctor said that I would go for an operation because he saw a fibroid.
I said, "No, I will not go for an operation".
He asked why.
I said that I did not want to go for an operation.
He said that I should go for an operation that I should sign
but I said that I would not sign anything.
The day that I delivered the baby,
my husband dropped me at the hospital and I told him that he should go.
I was holding my Morning Water.
Before he got back, I delivered my baby and also the fibroids finally came out.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
You mean you delivered safely without any operation
and as the child came out, the fibroid also came out at that moment?
Yes.
I used the Morning Water all over my body and prayed.
Before my husband came, I had already delivered the baby successfully.
They called him on the phone and when he came, he was screaming and shouting.
He said, "Are you sure he is my boy?" I said, "Yes, he is your son".
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus one more time!
Generally, madam: Just tell us - how have your lives changed since that word of prophecy,
both in terms of finances and the breakthrough that has come.
What can you testify about the changes that you and your husband have seen ever since then?
Our lives have really changed because that year, I was able to go for my youth service.
which was delayed since 2012.
There have been breakthroughs in our lives and also his business changed.
Thank You, Jesus Christ. Indeed, a million thanks are not enough
as the evidence of Christ Jesus is lives changed.
Now, madam, we can see a couple of documents on the board,
aside the picture of the car that your husband bought you.
Can you just show us what these documents are and what they are representing.
This is the scan showing that I was pregnant at eight months.
This is 'SY', showing that it is a male child.
These are the fibroids - the big one and the small one.
This is when I was pregnant
This is the car we were able to buy on December 10th.
Thank You, Jesus Christ! Let's put our hands together for Jesus one more time!
In the light of what Jesus Christ has done for you and your husband,
what is your word of advice to our viewers all over the world?
My advice to the viewers is that they should believe in God.
The God who blessed me will bless you too, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Christ Jesus!
Sir, finally, your own word of advice to our viewers all over the world.
My advice to the viewers all over the world is that they should believe in prophecies.
Believe in whatever the Man of God tells you.
If I did not have faith in that prophecy, I do not know how it would have turned out.
My advice to the whole world is to be always faithful in all your endeavours
and believe in God. He will see you through your predicaments.
Amen. One more time, let's put our hands together for Christ Jesus!
We also just want to hear a final word from our sister here because we haven't spoken to her yet.
Sister, can you just introduce yourself to us, tell us who you are to this family
and just tell us a word that you want to say about their testimony.
Praise the Lord!
My name is Nneka.
I really thank God for the life of my sister, for what God has done for her.
I really thank God. I appreciate God because it was not easy.
Anybody who has not passed through barrenness will not understand the meaning of barrenness.
There is no peace in the marriage when there is no child
but God did it for her and I am here to thank God for what He has done for her.
Amen. Let's put our hands together one more time for Jesus Christ!
We pray that God will give this family the grace to raise up this child in the ways of the Lord
so as he grows up, he shall not depart from it and we know that the best is yet to come in Jesus' name.